接啊 快 接电话啊
Pick up. Come on, pick up.
嘿 是我
Hey, it's me.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
我可以解释这一切
I can explain everything.
回电话给我
Call me.
不
No!
郑重声明：本作品之片源、字幕均来自互联网，仅供个人影视制作的学习、交流之用。版权归发行公司所有。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业营利用途，否则一切后果由该组织或个人承担。本字幕组不承担任何法律及连带责任！请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
海军
罪案
调查处
第十一季  第十集
翻译：伯爵挠头写论文 小末要冻成蛇精了 小末末
翻译：飞行猪 菲力牛排和提拉米苏 秋水冬流
校对：流年想一觉不醒 Morning
校对：蓉小张想泡温泉 K希望房东给点力
字幕特效/时间轴/压制：老东邪
军事顾问： Tom
& GA 字幕组
特别呈献 &
那么 这是你的医疗记录
Then there's your medical history...
魔鬼黑帮之ex大团圆
人寿保险的LI-90（表格）DA-93（表格）...
the LI-90 for life insurance, the DA-93...
你很幸运这只是临时的联合任务职位
You're lucky this is just a temp Joint Duty assignment.
【Joint Duty assignment是一个特定的职位
负责综合行动或者支援至少陆海空三个军事部门中的两个】
就剩下这点文件了
Just a few forms left.
像是个人行动须知
Like the Notification of Personnel Action,
TA-44（表格）和你的
the TA-44 and the background questionnaire
安全背景调查表
for your new security clearance.
-Roda -照这样下去
Roda. Bishop's gonna be useless
Bishop这周都别想工作了
for the next week.
我们应该救她吗
Should we rescue her?
No.
不
如果她不能解决Roda的话 Gibbs会给她醒醒脑
If she can't handle Roda, Gibbs is gonna melt her brain.
哦 我还需要
Oh! And I'm gonna need...
DD-817（表格） 尽快完成
the DD-817 ASAP.
【ASAP：as soon as possible的简写】
哦 这其实是6045版本
Oh, this is actually version 6045.
在DD-817（表格）上的v49是国防部管理的
The DoD is up to v49 on the DD-817.
黑色笔书写 不得修改
Black pen only, no smudges.
不要考验我的耐心...
And don't test me...
小菜鸟
kitty-cat.
我看到你们了 先生们
I can see you, gentlemen.
刚刚发生了什么
What just happened?
我做错什么了吗
Did I do something wrong?
不 你只是通过了第一次测验
No, you just passed your first test.
Roda是人力资源部门的奇葩
Roda, from HR-- legendary.
但不要太自以为是了
But don't get too cocky.
仍然要进行测谎
Still got to take that polygraph.
我还要进行另一个测谎
I have to take <i>another</i> polygraph?
恩 还有你得做的就是
Mm-hmm. And then all you have to do
在Leroy Jethro Gibbs探员手下生存下来
is survive Special Agent Leroy Jethro Gibbs.
也许你没听说过 这个人...他其实
In case you haven't heard, the man is... He's actually
现在就在你的身后
coming up behind you right now.
恩
Hmm.
你不该提醒他的
You're not supposed to do that.
我现在做了什么
What did I do now?
你交了我这个朋友
You've made a friend.
带上装备
Grab your gear.
在Potomac高地发现了海军尸体
Got a dead Marine in Potomac Heights.
你还在等什么 Bigshop
You waiting on something, Bishop?
我什么装备都没有
I don't have any gear.
好吧 那你开车
Good. You can drive.
那好
Okay.
Ron Flegman下士
Corporal Ron Flegman,
23岁 在Quantico外驻扎
23, stationed out of Quantico,
在车辆调配场工作
worked in the motor pool.
他一个人住在这
He live here alone?
楼上
Upstairs.
已经和他的指挥官谈  ======了
Already spoke with his CO.
不折不扣的海军 有很高的评价
Solid Marine, stellar evaluations.
没什么别的了
Not much else.
那么 如果这是行凶抢劫
Well, if this was a mugging,
这还真是糟糕的一个
it was a really bad one.
我们找到了一个目击者
We got a witness.
他看到有人
He saw someone enter
在枪击之前从这栋楼的后门进来
the back of the building just prior to the shooting.
多亏这只魔术手 我们甚至有了疑犯素描
We even got a sketch, courtesy of Magic Fingers here.
【Magic Fingers是儿童故事，此为Tony对Bishop的恭维】
你看看
Here you go.
是个小丑
That's a clown.
恩 是个街头表演者
Well, uh, a street performer, yes.
看 没太多的细节
See, there weren't very many details,
所以我用从趣味屋拿来的Jumpy作为模板
so I used Jumpy, from <i>Jumpy's</i> <i>Funhouse,</i> as a template.
Jumpy有这么大
Jumpy had this really big, like,
这样的红色的鼻子 而且他笑的时候
this, like, red nose, and when he smiled,
他...是我小时候
he... It was this kids show I used to watch,
常常看的儿童剧
when I was little.
恩 有人告诉我们
Um, we were told there were several street performers
这区有一些这样的街头表演者
who work the area.
运气够好的话 这个Jumpy小丑也许就在这工作
With any luck, maybe Jumpy the Clown had a permit.
去发证办公室核对下
Check the licensing office.
查清楚每个得到街头表演许可的小丑
Pull every permit on the block.
好极了
Nice.
哦 谢天谢地我们在室内
Oh, thank heavens we're indoors.
真是一个糟糕的周末
It's been a brutal week.
冻得我都没法发抖了
And I have a chill I just can't shake.
我也一样 有人介意我在这跳一跳取暖吗
Me too. Anybody mind if I do some jumping jacks?
【jumping jacks 跳跃运动，一种运动项目】
-介意 -介意 -介意
Yes. - Yes. Yes.
好 初步断定死因是
Well, preliminary cause of death appears to be
胸口上的两个枪伤
two gunshot wounds to the chest.
是的 从中距离射击
Yeah. From medium range.
恩 Bigshop小姐
Ah, Ms. Bishop.
你介意靠近一点
Would you care to take
看看伤口吗
a closer look at the wound?
呃...
Uh...
好吧
sure.
好
Yeah.
来看这个伤口
Note this one.
它是椭圆形的
It's oval in shape,
也就是说 那个子弹
which means that the bullet
以一定角度穿过他的皮肤
penetrated the skin at an angle.
恩 你能从那上面找到弹道吗
Huh. Can you get a trajectory from that?
可能的弹道 可以
Well, possible trajectory, yeah.
真聪明
Very astute.
还有 我们测量出体温
Also, we get a core temperature,
可以基本推定死亡时间
we can approximate time of death.
老大 他还有第二个手机
Boss, he's got a second cell phone.
手机里有什么
Anything on it?
它被密码锁定了
Well, it's password-locked,
但是看起来
but looks like he received
就在被杀之前
almost a dozen missed calls
他大概收到了12条未接来电
just prior to the shooting.
可能是有人在试着警告他
Maybe somebody was trying to warn him.
我知道这个号码
I know that number.
亚当之家酒店
Adams House hotel.
你爸爸不总是呆在那里吗
Doesn't your dad always stay there?
是的 但..
Yes, but...
不 不 不
no, no, no.
他正在300英里之外的
He's at a skin peel retreat,
皮肤护理会所 所以不可能
300 miles away, so there's no way.
你知道 半小时之内结的帐
You know, checkout's in half an hour.
打电话给受害者的人可能还在那里
Whoever called our victim might still be there.
MeGee 你去犯罪现场
McGee, you got the crime scene.
DiNozzo 跟我来
DiNozzo, with me.
好..
Uh...
那...那是...
that... that was...
太快了吧
that was fast.
是很快
Fast. Yeah.
经理说那个电话来自Smith先生登记的
Manager said the calls came from room 103.
103室
Registered to Mr. Smith.
我们像"alias"那样潜进去 你觉得怎么样
I'm gonna go with "alias"" what do you think?
【注：Alias是ABC史上最热播的电视剧之一，中文译作双面女间谍】
经理来开门吗
Manager coming to open it up?
不
No.
她给了我钥匙
She gave me the key.
由于距离结账只过了5分钟 严格来说
Since it's two minutes after checkout, technically,
我们有权利进去
we have a right to enter.
真有趣 那个看起来是你的前妻
That's funny, that looks like your ex-wife.
先来香槟 然后
Champagne first, and then...
再来一点点..
a little...
好吧 我这是要被捆绑调教了
Well, tie me up and call me Loretta.
哇
Wow.
哇塞
Wowzers.
这不是你们看到的那样
This is not what it looks like.
嗯 我们只是在...
Right. We were just...
别 我不想知道细节
No, I do not need the details.
我倒不介意知道点细节
I wouldn't mind a few details.
-好 听着 -住嘴 你怎么话这么多
Okay, look... Zip it, windbag. Not another word.
你在说什么 他们都看到了
What are you talking about? The cat is out of the bag.
如你们所想 行了吧
It just sort of happened, okay?
我们本打算告诉你的 但又必须保密 因为...
We were gonna tell you. We just kept it hush-hush because...
-她是有老公的人 -我们担心
She's married. Because we're concerned
Emily接受不了
that Emily won't take it well.
【Fornell和Diane的女儿】
她才13岁 这会让她
She's 13, this can be...
-很困惑 -而且Victor和我已经分居了
confusing. And Victor and I are separated,
我们在办离婚手续
we're getting a divorce.
该我们问你了 你丫的冲到我们的房间里干什么
Your turn. What the hell are you doing in our room?
-好说 死了一个海军
Well, we got a dead Marine.
有人从这个房间打了一个电话给他
His cell phone got a call from this room
-就在他被杀之前 -不可能啊
- just prior to his murder. - That's impossible.
我们从昨天晚上就在这个房间
We've been in this room since last night,
而且我都没有用过这里的电话
and I haven't used the phone.
这样啊  但我有种预感 她用过
Oh, but I'm getting a feeling she has.
Diane是你么
Diane...?
什么
Hmm?
我能只和你说么
Could I speak with you?
私下地
Privately?
-如果你想挨一枪 -好 我说
If you'd like to be shot. Okay, fine.
我用过电话
I used the phone.
但不是打给什么海军
But not to call some Marine.
我是想打给我男朋友Eddie
I was trying to call my boyfriend Eddie.
哦 真搞笑 你貌似说了男朋友
Oh, that's funny. It sounded like you said boyfriend.
好吧 是前男友 刚刚我想打电话跟他分手
Well, ex-boyfriend, now. I was calling to break it off.
当我在洗澡的时候
While I was in the bathtub?
所以说洗澡的那会儿 你还是有男朋友的
You had a boyfriend while I was in the bathtub?
但他一直没接
But he never picked up.
这么说来 你不认识下士Ron Flegman
So, you don't know Private Ron Flegman?
搞不好是她的未婚夫呢  这简直难以置信
It's probably her fiancée. This is unbelievable.
没有 我从没听过那个名字
No, I've never heard that name in my life.
等会 你知道么...
No, you know what?
你需要冷静冷静
You need to calm down.
你刚刚自己也说了  咱俩的事就是“自然而然”的发生了
You just said it yourself; this just sort of happened.
所以说 好吧 你遇见我时
So, yes, fine, you caught me.
我是一直在和别人约会
I was dating someone else.
但是 这仅仅是与上段恋情产生了一点点无知的重叠
But, you know, it was a little, innocent overlap.
哈
Hah!
关于受害人为什么会有你男朋友的手机
Any idea why our victim would
你有什么想法么
have your boyfriend's cell phone?
是前男友 而且我不知道
Ex-boyfriend, and no.
但是 我得说
But, you know, I gotta say,
如果Eddie把自己的手机跟那个死掉的家伙的弄混了
I'm not that surprised that Eddie is mixed up
我是一点也不惊讶 因为 嗯
with some dead guy, because, um,
我的意思是 呃 他很 有趣
I mean, huh, he was, he was fun.
-我不用知道的这么详细  -但是 好吧
I don't need the details. But the, yeah,
有些事情不太对劲
there was, something wasn't right.
我发现他总在撒谎
I kept catching him in these lies and...
而且他没有信用记录
he has no credit history.
-每个人都应该有信用记录  -行了 对我而言足够了
Everybody has a credit history. Well, that's enough for me.
走 我们去把他抓了
Let's go arrest him.
不行 我们得先找他谈谈
Oh, no. We're gonna talk to him first.
我就知道你会这么说
I knew you were gonna say that.
犯罪现场已经封锁了
Crime scene's locked up.
我就顺便来看看
Thought I'd come by and se...
哇..
Whoa.
你好，小McGee
Hi, Chucky.
看什么看
What?
这么说Fornell曾经娶了Gibbs的前妻
So, Agent Fornell was married to Gibbs's ex-wife?
没错
Yup.
并且我们在犯罪现场发现的
And the owner
第二部手机的主人
of the second cell phone from our crime scene
也在和Gibbs的前妻约会
was dating Gibbs's ex-wife?
-对 -哇
Yup. Whew, wow.
真是太巧了
That's quite a coincidence.
对啊 的确很巧
I know. It really is.
你知道吗 真的很难想象
You know, it's hard to imagine
居然有女人同时喜欢Fornell和这个叫Eddie的人
the same woman liking Fornell and this Eddie guy.
也许Diane喜欢他是因为他和Fornell一点也不像
Although, maybe Diane liked him because he's not Fornell.
最好把心理分析的活留给Ducky做
Best leave the psychoanalysis to Ducky.
如果你还珍爱生命的话
If you value breathing.
Bishop 你怎么不警告我一下
Bishop, you could have warned me.
你之前说我不该那样做
You said I wasn't supposed to do that.
Tobias 你好啊
Tobias. Hey.
你在这干什么
What are you doing here?
只是觉得你也许需要些帮助
Just thought you might need some help.
Diane很担心
Diane's really worried, I just want to
我过来这里她可能心里好受一点
put her mind at ease.
啊哈 这样
Yeah, uh-huh.
你在轮船上的厨房打了我一枪
You shot me in the caboose.
你欠我的
You owe me.
McGee
McGee.
开始
Go.
哦
Oh.
好的
Okay.
这是Eddie Macklin
Uh, meet Eddie Macklin.
Diane Sterling的男朋友
Diane Sterling's... boyfriend.
前男朋友
Ex-boyfriend.
他31岁
He's 31 years old
在一家本地的攀岩健身房工作
and works at a local climbing gym.
嗯 然后呢
Yeah, and...?
就这么多了 我们能找到的所有信息都是从六个月前开始的
And that's it, we couldn't find anything
因为六个月之前 这个人不存在
prior to six months ago.
没有停车收据 借书卡 公交通票
No parking ticket, library card or bus pass.
有点意思
Interesting.
让我们直接问问他呗
Let's go ask him about it.
天啊
God...
对 我认识他
Yeah, I knew him.
大概六个月之前他来找工作
He came in about six months ago, looking for a job.
他教基础攀岩班
He teaches our Basic Climb class.
哇哦
Whoa.
-他的胸比Diane还要大 -你知道他现在在哪么
His chest is bigger than Diane's. You know where he is?
不知道 实际上他还放了了今天早上私人课程的鸽子
No. And he actually blew off a private lesson this morning.
而且我也不认为Eddie喜欢教学生
But I don't think Eddie was a big fan of the student.
那这个家伙呢
How about this guy?
你认识他么
You know him?
对 就是他
Yeah, that's him.
他是Eddie的学生
That's Eddie's student.
神啊 发生什么了
Geez, what happened?
Flegman下士被枪杀了
Corporal Flegman was shot.
我们在他身上发现了Eddie的手机
We found Eddie's cell phone on him.
我们想跟他谈谈
We'd like to talk to him about it.
当然还有一些其他的事
Among other things.
我知道Eddie是个麻烦
I knew Eddie was trouble.
总感觉他不太对劲
Just something off about him.
你知道我们在哪能找到他
You know where we can find him?
我不知道 他的公寓吧
I don't know-- his apartment?
哦 已经空了
Uh, it's empty.
车管所没有他的车辆登记记录
No car registration with the DMV.
那就奇怪了 他是有车的
That's weird. He has a car.
我在他的就职申请上看到的
I got the info on his employment application.
-我去拿一下  -谢谢
Let me get it. Thanks.
嫌疑人的车是辆88年的银色林肯城市轿车
Yeah, suspect's vehicle is an '88 silver Lincoln Town Car.
华盛顿的牌照
it's a DC plate.
让Bishop接手你的活
Have Bishop run the BOLO.
-你确定 -对
You sure? Yeah.
这就去办
On it.
要吃点么
Grab a bite?
我还好
I'm good.
啤酒呢
Beer?
漫长的一天呀 Tobias
Long day, Tobias.
Gibbs 我到底在干嘛呢
What the hell am I doing, Gibbs?
我感觉我被一条蟒蛇吞下 没有退路
I feel like I've been swallowed by a python, cut my way out
只能再向蟒蛇肚子更深处爬去
and then crawled back inside again.
-听上去挺对的 -嘿 别这样
Sounds about right. Oh, come on.
我们都犯了错误
Are we making a mistake?
你想要什么
What are you looking for?
不是你理解的那样 不是只有性
Not just sex, if that's what you're getting at.
-哇 哇哦 别说了 -但是别这样误解我
Whoa. Whoa. Stop. But don't get me wrong, no,
-这不只是... -别说了行么
it's better than... Just stop.
我只是想说这次有些东西变得不一样了
I'm just saying that there's something different this time.
也许是因为我们已经是前任的关系
Maybe because we're exes.
你也应该试一试 我是说
You should try it. I mean...
和你其他的前妻
with another one of your ex-wives,
不是这一个 这个我已经...要了
not this one, 'cause this one's... taken.
我现在能回家了么
Can I go home now?
你真是我遇到最糟糕的情感顾问
You are the worse advice giver I've ever met!
别就这么走了
Don't quit your day job.
我想
I think...
只要你们都觉得幸福 这就够了
as long as you're happy, that's all that matters.
开心？
Happy?
【此处Tobias理解为开心】
跟这些有什么关系
What's that got to do with anything?
是我的邻居
It's my neighbor.
她帮忙照看Emily
She watches Emily.
她现在在干什么
What'd she do now?
不 我得走了
No, I'll go.
她又没回来吃晚饭
She didn't come home for dinner again.
这周第三次了
Third time this week.
我得搜遍整个购物广场来找她
I've got to go prowl the mall looking for her.
嘿
Hey.
下次请你吃饭
Rain check?
我能等
I can wait.
如果他们俩要复合
No way in hell am I living with either of them,
我绝对不会跟他俩一起生活
if they're back together.
我能在你家多住一晚吗 Gibbs叔叔
Can I stay one more night at your house, Uncle Gibbs?
我们可以一起重温《非洲女王》
We can watch <i>African Queen</i> again.
你父母希望你回家
Your parents want you back.
他们昨晚可一点没想起让我回家
They didn't want me back last night.
我13岁了 如果我能搭车去木星
I'm 13-- they'd let me emigrate to Jupiter
他们倒希望我能移民到那儿
if I could get a ride.
早上好 我将Eddie Macklin的
Morning. I entered Eddie Macklin's
车辆信息还有外貌特征
vehicle information into the NCIC database,
输入了NCIC数据库
along with a physical description.
然后 我给所有的执法部门发了副本
Then I sent out copies to all law enforcement agencies.
-Bishop -然后 嗯 我觉得
-Bishop And then I-I just felt like... Bishop.
你可以直接说 “协查通告发布完毕”
You can just say "BOLO's out."
嗯
Uh...
协查通告发布完毕
BOLO's out.
他告诉我 你其实表现的很出色
He actually told me you're doing great,
不过你需要放松一点
but you need to relax a little.
我太同意了
Can't say I disagree.
Emily 谢谢你的关心
Emily. Thank you.
小姐 你知不知道
Do you have any idea what kind of trouble
自己闯了什么祸
you are in, missy?
我
Me?!
是你把自己的生活弄得一团糟
You're the one who's ruining your life.
你再说一次
I beg your pardon?
嗯 你跟爸爸又搞在一起了
Uh, www.you-and-dad-suck- together.com?
还是你现在对婚姻太绝望 无法顾及到这一点
Or are you too desperate at this point to care?
有其母必有其女 哈
Apple doesn't fall far from the tree, huh?
你怎么能这么跟我说话
How dare you talk to me like that.
你跟爸爸沟通过没
You and Dad speak to each other?
你们在一块 只有争吵
All you guys do is fight.
我们才不争吵呢
We do not fight.
我们只是嗓门大了点
We are just very loud!
最好让她们俩闹个筋疲力尽
Best let them wear each other out before I get
然后我再加入争论  -对了 还有你
- into it. - Right. And you!
你怎么能这么对我
How could you do this to me?
宝贝
Honey,
没有人在欺负你
no one is doing anything to you.
你母亲跟我 只不过
Your mother and I are just...
等等
Wait a second.
你怎么知道
How exactly do you know about...
你母亲跟我复合的事情
your mother and me?
所有的事情 我都知道
I know everything.
我在你们俩的脸书账户里 安装了击键记录程序
I put a keystroke logger on both your Facebook accounts.
你干了什么 你需要有法院的许可
You what?! You need a warrant
才能这么做
to do that!
Gibbs, Gibbs, Gibbs,
Gibbs, Gibbs, Gibbs.
我破解了嫌疑人的手机
I cracked the suspect's cell phone.
手机里有一大堆
There are boatloads of juicy texts on there
Fornell前妻发的情话
from him to Fornell's ex-wife.
我的意思是 这件事情比《五十度灰》还要古怪
I mean, this stuff is-is kinkier than <i>Fifty Shades of Grey.</i>
【注：《五十度灰》，一部情色小说】
你得过来看看
You have got to come see this...
Fornell你好
Fornell.
Fornell的前妻你好
Ex-wife.
Fornell的女儿你好
Daughter.
哎呀
Oops.
你给我回来
You get back here or I will smash
-要不然我就把实验室里的所有计算机都砸了 -不许碰我的宝贝计算机
every computer in that lab! Don't you touch my babies!
我可以申请（到你家）庇护吗
Can I apply for asylum?
Abbs 我希望你能让Gibbs一个人过来
Abbs, I hope you told Gibbs to come alone
如果Fornell看到这些短信 他肯定气炸了
'cause Fornell's head would explode if he saw these texts.
-有多远躲多远 -Tony 如果你还想活命
Better get a mop. Tony! If you value your life,
就马上把电脑关了
you will turn off that computer right now!
你要是敢碰电脑 我就跟你不客气了
Touch that CPU and I touch you.
我听不到你们说什么
I can't hear you.
我鼻窦感染了
I have a sinus infection.
我要去拿我的洗鼻壶
I have to go get my neti pot.
不 不 哦
No, no. Oh...
嘿 怎么不见了
Hey, what happened?
我早就未雨绸缪 防止任何紧急情况
I'm prepared for any contingency.
你干扰了一项正在进行的调查
You are interfering in an ongoing investigation.
把电脑重新打开
Turn that computer back on.
好吧 Tobias
Okay, Tobias,
大部分短信 是在我们
I sent most of those texts before you and I
复合之前发的
were back together again,
因此 这些短信是不能看的
so... they're inadmissible.
好 那就把我们复合之后
Okay. Just show me the texts
这位"Mata Hari"发的短信拿出来
that Mata Hari here sent after we got our game on.
【注：Mata Hari，历史上著名的双重女间谍】
让我们看看 你是多么无辜的 不凑巧的跟我们同时交往
Let's see how innocent that innocent overlap really was.
-还有人活着吗 -有 就是受了重伤
Everybody still alive? Yes, just wounded.
-因为她背叛了我 -Emily在哪儿
By betrayal. Where's Emily?
在会议室 跟Bishop在一块  她很好
Conference room with Bishop. And she's fine.
除了Diane的短信之外 你还有收获吗
You got anything besides Diane's texts?
有
Yeah.
嗯 嫌疑犯发了几条信息
The suspect, um, sent a few texts of his own.
他提到 他在当地银行有一个保险箱
He mentioned a safety deposit box at a local bank.
-信息发给谁了 -不知道 一个用黑市号码的
-Who'd he send them to? -A burn phone
【注：burn phone是一种预付费电话，廉价
不能被追踪，经常被用来从事非法活动 】
未注册手机
with a black market number.
所以说 肯定有些什么事情 正在进行当中
So something is definitely afoot here.
银行的名字查到了吗
You got the name of the bank?
我们去查一下
Let's go check it out.
喔 别着急
Whoa. Slow down.
我要让Diane一起去
I want Diane to come along
这样她就可以从银行监控录像上 指认她的前男友
so she can I.D. her ex-boyfriend from the security tapes.
-那又如何？-所以我不会
So? So I'm not
把你们俩都带上
bringing both of you.
锁匠已经差不多打开了保险箱
The locksmith is almost finished with the safe deposit box.
我去查看下监控录像
Let me go check on the security footage.
你想喝点什么
Would you like something to drink?
不用了 谢谢
No, I'm good.
白开水 配上吸管
I'll take a water. One straw,
加两片冰 三片柠檬
two pieces of ice, three slices of lemon.
Jethro 我到底在干什么
Jethro, what the hell am I doing?
我感觉自己开车开到沟里了
I feel like I drove into a ditch, towed my car out
然后我把车拖出来 又开到沟里了
and then drove right back in again.
老天 不要把我卷进来
Oh, God, please don't make me do this.
这都是你的错
This is all your fault.
-我的错误 -要不是你射中了Tobias的屁股
What? If you hadn't shot Tobias in the ass,
我就不用去护理他 导致旧情复燃
I wouldn't have had to nurse him back to health.
他太脆弱了
He was so vulnerable.
你要知道 他的自尊受到了严重伤害
You know, his pride was so wounded and...
直到有一天晚上 我帮他洗澡
Then one night I was helping him with his bath...
喔
Whoa.
喔 别说了
Whoa. Stop.
别说了
Stop. What is wrong
你们俩怎么了
with you two? I just need to know
我只想知道 你觉得我们是不是犯了个错误
if you think we're making a mistake.
这得看情况而定 呃
It depends. Uh...
你们到底要什么
What are you... looking for?
我只是想
I just want to...
清晨能够在我的爱人身边醒来
wake up next to someone I love.
这是Macklin先生的保险箱
Here's Mr. Macklin's safe deposit box
和监控录像
and the security footage.
谢谢你
Thank you.
他一个月之前租了这个保险箱
He rented the box a month ago.
在那之后有很多次操作
There's been a lot of activity since then.
-说说有多少操作 -过去的3个星期里
Define "a lot." He's been here
他一个人来了十几趟
over ten times in the last three weeks alone.
好
Well,
谁会在保险箱里就存些信纸呢
who stores stationery in a safe deposit box?
也许上一次他来的时候 换掉了一部分重要的物品
Perhaps he removed the important contents on his last visit.
让我们看看他上一次来的情况
Let's see his last visit.
哦 那是Eddie
Oh, that's Eddie right there
看上去他什么也没带
He doesn't appear to be carrying anything.
这个女人是谁
Who the hell is she?
好像是他女朋友
Looks like a girlfriend.
女朋友
Girlfriend?
我们约会的时候 他还有女朋友
While we were dating?
这个脚踏两只船的
That two-timing
臭不要脸...-嘿 Diane
son of a... Hey. Diane.
你跟Eddie约会的同时
While you were dating Eddie,
不是也在跟Fornell约会
you and Fornell were...
算了 不说这个了
Oh... forget it.
她有没有签名
Did she have to sign in, too?
没有 只有保险箱的所有者有签名
No, just the box's owner.
好 我们得找到这个女人
Well, we're gonna have to find her.
我们会找到的 放松点
We will. Relax.
她是我们找到Eddie的唯一线索
She's our only lead to Eddie.
子弹碎片在髋臼周围反弹
<i>The bullet fragment</i>
飞入髂骨
bounced around the acetabulum, flew up to the iliac crest...
在子弹射出人体之前 略低于尾骨 我要告诉你的是
Before exiting just below the coccyx. I'm telling you,
博士 这让人很震惊
Doctor, it's amazing.
让我来猜猜 肯尼迪神奇子弹理论说
Let me guess. The JFK Magic Bullet Theory?
哦 实际上是Fornell探员的屁股
Oh, ac-actually it's... Agent Fornell's heinie.
哦
Oh.
呃 我很抱歉 哦
Uh, I'm sorry. Uh...
何其荣幸 什么风把你吹来了
to what do we owe the pleasure?
哦 呃 荣幸 不敢当
Ooh. Uh, pleasure, no. But, uh,
我是想多接触一下
I do need to better familiarize myself with...
尸体
actual dead people.
真正的死尸
Who are dead.
我觉得 你们可以帮助我
I thought you might be able to help me.
你来对地方了
You've come to the right place.
跟Ron Flegman下士再打个招呼吧
Say hello again to Corporal Ron Flegman.
你好
Hello.
我们确认 枪击是死亡原因
We confirmed that the gunshots were the cause of death,
但是 这才开了个头
but that is really just the start.
比如说
For example, the, uh...
人死之后身体呈现灰色 表明受害者在谋杀后
Postmortem lividity on the body indicates that the victim
没有被移动
wasn't moved after the murder.
正确
That-that is... that is correct.
呃 然而
Uh, however,
他小腿前面的淤青
the bruise on the front of his calf there,
表明他
it indicates that...
有糖尿病
He was diabetic.
类脂质渐进性坏死 学名应该是这个
Necrobiosis lipoidica, I think it's called.
也答对了
That's also correct.
这个周末 我阅读了《尸检实务手册》
I took the liberty of reading the <i>Handbook of Autopsy Practice</i> this weekend.
你读完了
The whole thing?
有600多页
It's-it's over 600 pages.
实际上 是596页
It was 596, actually.
是本很棒的书
It was really cool.
祝你第一次正式
Happy first official joint duty
【此处Tony在模仿生日快乐歌】
联合任务愉快
BOLO to you.
这是个非常特别的时刻
It's a very special moment.
把蜡烛吹了 许个愿
Blow out the candle. Make a wish.
我发的有关Eddie Macklin 的协查通报有信儿了
My BOLO on Eddie Macklin came in?
你的愿望成真了
Your wish came true.
机场警察在一个长期停车的地方
Ah. Airport police found his car
找到了他的车子
in a long-term parking facility.
太好了 我们去找车子吧
Rock on. Let's go get it.
嗯 我们去
Mm. We are.
你留在这
You aren't.
测谎员跟你
You have a little appointment
有个小约会
with the polygraph person.
已经订好了
Already?
别担心 过程会很有趣的
Don't worry. It's gonna be fun.
测谎
Polygraphs...
有谁不喜欢谈论自己呢
Who doesn't love talking about themselves?
我刚刚把Emily送到学校
I was dropping Emily off at school.
听说你找到Diane前任小男友的车子了
I heard you found Diane's ex-boy-toy's car.
对 他把车扔在了机场的一个长期停车场里
Yeah, he left it in long-term parking at the airport.
一大堆破烂玩意
What a pile of junk.
女人没有羞耻心吗
Hath the woman no shame?
你能相信Eddie的年龄还不到Diane的一半么
Can you believe he's half her age?
亲爱的 我觉得你还不够貌美
I guess you weren't stallion enough, Chuckie.
【讽刺McGee没有被Diane看上】
Fornell探员 我发誓 我们从来没有
Agent Fornell, I swear, we never...
对 Diane也是这么说的 我相信了她
Yeah. Diane told me the same thing, and I believed her,
尽管目前的情况给她的信用泼了冷水
though current circumstances are throwing a bit of cold water on her credibility.
你们查了机场的航班吗
You run down the flights out of the airport?
查了  Eddie Macklin不在乘客名单上
Yes. There's no Eddie Macklin listed.
那他为什么把车停在那儿
So why was he parked there?
还有更多疑问呢
That's not the half of it.
我们不仅在车里发现了小丑的鼻子
Not only did we find a clown nose in the trunk
还有血迹
but we also found blood on...
Abby 我们应该等Gibbs回来再说
Abby. We're supposed to wait for Gibbs to get back.
对 当我没说
Oh, right. Never mind.
你们在车里找到了血迹
You found blood in the car?
无处不在
Minute traces of it everywhere.
我们认为 有人试图将血迹清理干净
We think someone tried to clean it up.
不过我还是可以检测到血蛋白
But I was still able to detect blood proteins
至少有4个不同的受害者
from at least four separate victims.
什么 你是说Diane的前男友
What... You're saying that Diane's ex
是个连环杀手
was some kind of serial killer?
那
That's...
我们调查了
We interviewed all the street performers
Flegman下士被杀的这个区
licensed in the area
所有持照的街头艺人
where Corporal Flegman was killed.
他们都有不在场证明
They all had alibis.
同样也都有一双非常大的鞋子
And very large shoes.
与此同时 就剩下了一个
At the moment, that leaves
嫌疑犯 Diane Sterling的
one remaining suspect. Diane Sterling's
前男友 同时也是
ex-lover, and owner
一辆沾满血迹的林肯车的主人
of a Lincoln with multiple blood stains in it.
喂 Diane
What, Diane?
你们现在找到他了么
Well, have you found him yet?
没有 我们还能没找到他
No, we have not found him yet.
答案和你前四次打电话来一样
It's the same answer as the last four times when you called.
我们在这辆车上找到间接证据
We found circumstantial evidence
能够把他和Flegman被杀联系起来
in this car linking him to Flegman's murder,
但是现在还没有他的下落
but no indication of his current whereabouts.
Tobias么 你没有和Diane在一起么
What, Tobias? Aren't you with Diane?
你是不是试图隐瞒什么
Are you holding anything back?
没有 我没有任何事瞒着你
No, I am not holding anything back.
等我有所发现时我会告诉你的
I will tell you when I have something.
好
Fine.
噢 真不敢相信我会对这里的测谎如此担忧
Oh, I can't believe I was so worried about that polygraph.
我的意思是 在NSA 他们会问你所有事情
I mean, at NSA, they ask you everything.
【注：NSA National Security Agency美国国家安全局】
几乎是 所有事情
As in, like, everything.
我真是惊讶你们这的测谎没问的那么详细
I'm surprised you guys don't have,
比如说 有更多的人事问题关于怎么能…
like, more personnel issues with how...
我好像打断了什么
I am interrupting something.
你想让我离开么
Do you want me to leave?
不 我想让你工作
No. I want you to work.
这意味着我们得把我们知道的全部告诉她
That means we tell him what we know.
到目前为止 对那个神秘女郎的面部识别
Oh. So far, no luck using facial recognition
没有任何结果
to track our mystery woman.
我仍会继续追查下去
I'm still working on it.
Abby也没有
And Abby hasn't gotten any hits
在Eddie车里采集到的血液样本上发现任何线索
on the blood samples we found in Eddie's car.
只知道是五个不同的受害人
Total is five individuals.
好的 扩大协查范围
All right, expand the BOLO.
我要让这家伙的照片
I want this guy's photo
出现在每一个火车站 和每一个汽车站
in every train station, in every bus station.
这个主意糟透了
That's a bad idea.
哦 不
Uh-oh...
我的意思是 或许我有个更好的主意
I mean... I might have a better idea.
是这样的 我认为Eddie会回来的
Look, Eddie is coming back.
若是弃车而逃的话 一定会找一个比机场停车场
If he was ditching his car, there are easier places
更隐蔽的地方
to abandon it than at an airport.
我们应该把车放回去并且密切监视
We should put it back and watch it,
当他来把车开走时
and when he comes to pick it up...
我们就能抓捕他
We grab him.
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
我们应该跟着他 看他会做什么
We follow him, see what he does,
他要去哪里 然后逮捕他
where he goes, then we grab him.
这个主意不错
Works for me.
我第一个轮班（监视车）
I got the first shift.
不要告诉任何人我在哪里
Don't tell anybody where I am.
-嘿 -哦
- Hey. -  Oh!
为什么你总是随身带着枪
Why do you always go for the gun?
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
别担心 我会走的
Well, don't worry, I'm not gonna stay.
我知道 我问的不是这个
I know. It wasn't the question.
Tobias和我计划着举办一次家庭聚餐 和Emily一起
Tobias and I had a family dinner planned with Emily,
但是她给我们留下消息 说她有另外的应酬
and she left us a message, saying she had other plans,
我以为她会到你这来
so I thought maybe she'd come back here.
去商场找找看
Try the mall.
这正是我现在想去的地方 多谢
Yes, that's where I'm going right now, thank you.
等我找到她我会通知你的
I will let you know.
希望你和你的枪相处愉快
I hope you and your gun have fun together.
真难以置信她居然没发现我
Can't believe she missed me.
为什么他们不在搜索房间的时候检查下壁橱
Who doesn't check the closet when they're clearing a house?
谁又会藏在壁橱里
Who doesn't turn off their cell phone
却不关手机
when they're hiding in a closet?
不是我的手机响
Wasn't my cell phone.
我忘了我在手表上设置了闹钟
I forgot I set my Happy Cat Friend Alert Watch
提醒我收看
to let me know when the <i>Columbo</i> marathon
今晚Columbo马拉松比赛
started tonight.
你应该和你妈妈说一声 她很担心
Have to tell your mom. She's worried.
我知道 我知道的 给我两分钟
I know. I know. Just give me two minutes.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
好吧 你需要什么
All right, what do you need?
我希望你能劝劝我的父母 让他们分手
I want you to help me convince my parents to break up.
他们会听你的
They listen to you.
你知道的 他们不适合
And you know they aren't right for each other.
你也看到过他们吵架
You've seen them fight.
他们经常吵架么
They fighting a lot?
当然 甚至在公众场所
In public, yeah.
就好像他们对吵架情有独钟
It's like they have a fetish for it.
但是 我想 若是只有我们三个在一起的话
But... when it's just the three of us,
情况也不是那么糟糕
it's not so bad, I guess.
但是你知道最后也不会有好结果的
But you know this will end badly.
好吧 也许会
Well, yeah, it might.
接着我又会看到他们再次离婚
Then I get to watch them break up all over again.
噢  我有点混乱了
Oh, I... I'm confused.
你 你  不希望他们在一起么
You-you-you don't want them together?
或者说你害怕他们再次分手么
Or you're scared that they're gonna break up again?
我怎么会害怕他们分手呢
Why would I be scared of that?
这正是我所希望的
It's what I want!
额 等等
Uh... Wait.
现在我也混乱了
Now <i>I'm</i> confused.
你可真不擅长做这个
You suck at this!
你好 我是Gibbs
Yeah, it's Gibbs.
Bishop和我在机场
Bishop and I are at the airport.
Eddie回来了 他开走了他的车
Eddie's back. He picked up his car.
我们正在跟踪他
We're tailing him now.
好的 跟下去 随时通报
Yeah, stay with it. Let me know.
会的
Will do.
孩子 两分钟到了
Two minutes are up, kid.
让我送你回家
Let's get you home.
说一下现在的状况
Give me a sit-rep.
Eddie整夜都开着车
Eddie drove all night.
我觉得他是在侦查是否有人跟踪他
I think he was trying to see if he had a tail.
最后他到了这里 停下车
He finally came here, parked his car
然后消失了
and disappeared.
Fornell正带着后援赶来
Fornell's covering the rear.
好的 DiNozzo 你和我来
Okay. DiNozzo, you're with me.
McGee Bishop 你们到出口处
McGee, Bishop, you got the exit.
没有人
We're clear.
看起来可真像汉尼拔·莱克特的业余爱好中心
Looks like Hannibal Lecter's little hobby center.
【注：汉尼拔·莱克特，《沉默的羔羊》系列里的变态杀手】
老大
Boss.
我来搞定
I got this.
嘿 我们是NCIS的
Hey! NCIS.
趴在地上 把手放在头上
Get on the ground, put your hands on your head!
你觉得你能跑到哪去
Where do you think you're going?
哦 得了吧
Oh, come on.
FBI高级探员 Tobias Fornell
Senior FBI Agent Tobias Fornell.
我相信你认识我的妻子
I believe you know my wife.
他这是又想来打我了么
Is he gonna hit me again?
不
No. And...
很抱歉我打了你
And I apologize for that.
我们真的只是需要和你谈谈
We just really needed to talk to you.
好吧 谈些什么
Yeah, about what?
你不是应该问问发生了什么吗
Aren't you gonna ask what happened?
Flegman是你的学生
Flegman was a student of yours.
发生了什么
What happened?
你睡了我老婆
You slept with my wife!
发生了什么… 就是…
What happened... was that...
你的学生被杀害了 他身上还带着你的手机
your student was murdered... with your cell phone on him.
然后你消失了
And then you disappeared.
为什么你的车里
Why is your car
到处都是血迹
covered with blood?
你又如何解释你的那些"恐怖收藏品"
And what's with that little shop of horrors we found you in?
噢 那个储物间 那不是我的 哥们
Oh, that storage unit-- that ain't mine, bro.
那么我想这个也不是你的咯
Oh, I suppose this isn't yours, either.
我们在储物柜里找到20多卷钱
We found 20 more of those hidden in the storage unit.
差不多10万美金
That's almost 100 grand.
对一个健身教练来说这可是一大笔现金
It's a lot of cash for a gym teacher.
我要出去
I need to get out of here.
现在就离开这 如果他以为是我拿了他的钱
Now. If he thinks I took off with his money...
谁
Who?
你们不能逮捕我
You ain't arrested me.
你们只有间接证据
Everything you got is circumstantial.
我可以说有人在我的车里割破手指
So some people cut their fingers in my car.
你们找到别的尸体了吗  除了这个
You got any bodies, aside from this loser
在健身馆拿错电话的杯具男
who took the wrong cell phone at the gym?
我知道我的权利
I know my rights, man.
你要么逮捕我 要么就让我走
You got to arrest me or let me go.
难道不是吗 伙计
What's it gonna be, fellas?
我想就是这样的
Yeah, that's what I thought, too.
站住 喂 喂
Whoa, hold on. Hey! Hey!
这是什么
What is that?
你被捕了 我们的法鉴人员检测出
Arrest it is. Our forensic tech
你车里的血迹来自一个犯下多重谋杀罪的
traced the blood in your car to an unsolved
在逃杀人犯
quintuple homicide.
所以 给我坐下 你跟案子扯上关系了
So, sit down, you walking midlife crisis!
胡说 我没有杀人
This is nuts, man! I didn't kill anybody!
血迹是10年前的
That blood is ten years old!
这辆车被警察没收过
The car's from a police impound!
那你怎么开着
So how are you driving it?
因为我不是Eddie Macklin
'Cause my name isn't Eddie Macklin.
我是特别探员Edward McKenzie
It's Special Agent Edward McKenzie.
我为特勤局工作
I work for the Secret Service.
你们两个将要搞砸一项已经持续了6个月的高度机密行动
And you two are about to blow a highly-classified six-month op.
我们的经济犯罪科
Our financial crimes division
这几年一直在调查一起
has been working a money-laundering case
洗钱的案子
for over year.
我们查到高塔健身馆有一个现金交易点
We traced one of the sources of the cash to the Tower Gym.
我在那里做卧底
I went in undercover.
发现这些现金来自
Found out the cash came
一个专门抢劫银行的帮派
from a bank-robbery gang run by the owner,
老板是Elijah Banner和他的女朋友
Elijah Banner, and his girlfriend.
这就是我们在银行的监控录像上看到的神秘女人
There's our mystery woman from the bank.
Elijah让我去那里租一个保险箱
Elijah told me to rent a safe deposit box there
这样我和她就能来这里为下一次抢劫踩点
so she and I could case the place.
你也在追求她吗
Oh, were you casing her, too?
抱歉 各位
Sorry, guys.
老大 她就像只猫 当她发现
Boss, she's like a cat. When she found out...
你好 Diane
Hello, Diane.
噢 我听说咱俩分手了
Oh, I heard we broke up.
真遗憾
Sorry about that.
对了 我是特勤局的探员
Oh, and I'm a Secret Service agent.
我听说了 你这是什么态度
I heard. What's with the attitude?
我不知道 可能是因为你跟你前夫
I don't know. Maybe it's, you were sleeping...
在我们约会期间 滚床单了
...with your ex-husband while we were dating.
喂
Hey.
他说到点子上了
Man has a point.
噢
Oh...
你们现在成一伙的了
You guys are buddies now?
是的 我们正考虑合开一家“前任”俱乐部
Yeah. We were thinking of starting a club.
是吗
Yeah?
那好吧 听着
Well, watch it, boys.
我知道你们每个人所有的
I know something about each and every one of you
你们不想让别人知道的事
that you don't want anybody else to know.
我还有一个Twitter账号
And I got a Twitter account.
我们得回去工作了
We need to get back to work.
呃
Uh...
喂 放开我
Hey, let go of me!
- 快点 - 把你的手拿开
- Come on! - You take your hands off me
- 马上 - 不好意思
- right now! - Sorry.
- 马上 - 得罪了
- right now！ - Well... ry.
Flegman下士怎么会卷入这件事
So, how was Corporal Flegman involved?
Flegman负责驾车逃跑
Flegman drove the getaway car,
但是Elijah觉得他是个废柴
but Elijah thought he was skimming.
看来Elija最后还是解决了他
Looks like Elijah finally did something about it.
你为什么没逮捕他
Why haven't you taken this guy down?
他把自己撇的很干净
He keeps his hands too clean.
我们这次秘密行动就是要逮捕他
We need to catch him in the act.
当你们抓我的时候
When you picked me up,
我正为他的下次抢劫采购装备
I was collecting gear for his next robbery.
但要是Elijah觉得我带着他的钱跑了
But if Elijah thinks I took off with his money,
这6个月的努力就全都白费了
six months of work goes down the drain.
我们能以谋杀Flegman的罪名逮捕他
We can get him for Flegman's murder.
绝对不可能是他亲自动手
No way he pulled the trigger.
我觉得会是他的女朋友
I'm guessing it was his girlfriend.
她是个小丑 经常出现在小孩子的聚会上
She's the clown. Freelances at kids' parties.
我们要想抓住他 就得把钱放回去
We want to get this guy, we need to put the money back,
同时我也得回到街上去
and I need to get back on the street
在他注意到我消失之前
before he notices I'm gone.
是Elijah
It's Elijah.
他发现了
He's noticed.
我需要接这个电话
I got to answer it.
接吧 开扬声器
Yeah, put it on speaker.
嗨 E 什么事
Yo, E, what's the word, man?
别废话了 我知道你被收押了
Cut the bull, I know you got pinched.
把电话给Fornell探员
Put agent Fornell on the line.
探员Fornell
Agent Fornell.
你手上有我的东西 我手上也有你的东西
You got something of mine. I got something of yours.
爸爸 我在一辆白色的货车里 没有窗户 能闻到松树的味道
Dad, I'm in a white van, no windows, I can smell pine...
如果你还想再见到你的女儿
You ever want to see your daughter again,
就把我的钱还回来
you give me back my money.
保持联络
I'll be in touch.
我说的是我们能调动的所有人 所有设备
I said everybody, every asset we have.
老天爷啊 他抓了我的女儿
He's got my daughter, for God's sake.
我们发现储物箱里藏着一部相机
We found a camera hidden in the storage locker.
Elijah一定是这么发现我们拿了他的钱的
Must be how Elijah knew we had his money.
他看着我们收集证据
He watched us collect the evidence.
我们必须在他打电话前准备好
We need to be ready when he calls.
我的朋友都在待命 可以帮忙追踪打回来的电话
I have friends standing by to help trace the callback.
好 他的公寓已经清空了 他打算逃跑
Right. His apartment's been cleaned out, he's running.
协查通告有消息吗
Any word on the BOLO?
警察在拦截每一辆
Police are stopping every
无窗的白色厢式货车
windowless white van they see.
你的女儿很勇敢
Your daughter was very brave.
他们在厨房里发现了被打碎的窗户
They found a broken window in the kitchen.
他来过我们家
He was in our house.
一切都会没事的 宝贝
It's gonna be, it's okay, babe.
没事的 没关系
Okay. It's okay.
Emily会没事的
Emily's gonna be all right.
DiNozzo 你那里有什么消息
DiNozzo, what do you got?
Elijah的女朋友死了
Elijah's girlfriend is dead.
看上去是他把她勒死的
Looks like he's tying up loose ends.
有什么线索能查到他的位置么
You got any idea where he's going?
没有
Well, no,
但这次绑架绝对不是一时兴起
but he's not improvising.
我们发现Fornell和Emily被监视的照片
We found surveillance photos of Fornell and Emily.
Elijah应该早就开始制定出逃计划了
Elijah probably started making exit plans the moment
就在你俩出现在他工作室的时候
you two showed up at his studio.
绑架你的女儿他才能处于有利的位置
Zeroed in on your daughter as a lever he could pull.
无显示的电话
Blocked call.
tony 有消息马上通知
Tony, keep us posted.
好的
Will do.
探员Fornell
Agent Fornell.
我刚发了短信告诉你交涉的地点
I just texted you my location.
我要你派那个
I want you to send that girl.
清空我储物箱
The one who helped you clear out
的女孩过来
my storage locker.
她有八分钟的时间
She's got eight minutes to bring me
把我的钱带来 但只能让她自己来
my money, by herself.
一旦我安全离开 我就告诉你女儿的位置
Once I'm safely away, I'll tell you where you daughter is.
她现在很好 但是如果你想
She's fine. But if you even think
派其他的人来 我会发现的
of sending anyone else, I'll know.
你的女儿将会付出代价
And your daughter will pay the price.
好
Okay.
好  但你给我听好 尽管我们现在达成共识
Okay, but just so we're on the same page，
只要你敢碰我女儿一根头发
if so much as touch a hair on my daughter's head,
我发誓 我一定会找到你
so help me God, I will find you.
我会亲手把你的眼珠子挖出来
and I will rip your eyes out of your face
塞进你的喉咙
and shove them so far down your throat
那时你会需要一个直肠专家替你读晚报
you'll need a proctologist to read the evening paper.
他挂了
He hung up.
下一步怎么做 老大
What's the move, boss?
这是你的任务 Tobias
No, this is your call, Tobias.
Bishop 你是分析员
Bishop, you're the analyst.
如果我们给他钱 他会放过我的女儿吗
Is he gonna let my daughter go if we give him his money?
会的 他已经说明
Yes. He's demonstrated...
我知道了
I've got it.
我只想知道你能不能完成
I just need to know if you are up for this.
我可以
Yes.
那我们就把钱给他 Gibbs
Then we give him his money. Gibbs?
不设陷阱
No tricks.
你可以迟点再抓他
You can catch him later.
我们只想让女儿平安回来
We just want our daughter back.
一切正常
Comm check.
收到
Yeah, we read you.
你怎么样 Bishop
How you doing, Bishop?
我很好 有点出乎意料
I'm fine, surprisingly.
告诉Fornell探员我能做到
Tell Agent Fornell I can do this.
他正跟Diane在会议室里 但是我会告诉他的
He's in the conference room with Diane, but, will do.
好 那么
Okay, so...
我想我只要坐下来等着
I guess I just sit somewhere and wait?
不 继续走
No, keep moving.
避开监控盲区
Avoid a static blind spot.
记住 这个人是杀手
Remember, this guy's a killer.
你别让他偷袭你
You don't want him sneaking up on you.
好吧 现在感觉没那么好了
Okay, less fine now.
等等 我发现个人
Wait, I see something.
有个慢跑者过来了
There's a jogger approaching.
右边
Right build.
是他 没有白色货车
It's him, no white van.
好了
All right.
- 把钱倒进包里 - 好
- Dump the cash in here. - Okay.
Emily在哪
Where's Emily?
- 拿着这个 - 好
- Take this. - Okay.
- 在这等着 - 好
- Wait here. - Okay.
等我脱身了 我会打电话告诉你她的位置
When I'm clear, I'll call you with Emily's location.
交易结束
That was the deal.
好
Okay.
完成了
It's done.
我看不到他了
I've lost sight of him.
但是他给了我一个电话
But he gave me a cell phone,
说是会告诉我Emily的位置
said he was gonna call with Emily's location.
有办法找到这部电话曾在哪里被使用过吗
Any way to find out where that cell's been?
我们可以运行一下它的识别码
We can run its IMEI number.
好 如果我们找到它曾经出现在哪里 我们就有可能
Right. If we find out where it's been, we might be able
- 找到他去哪了 - 开始找吧
- to figure out where he's going. - Yeah, do it.
好的 这需要几分钟
Okay, uh, it'll just take a minute.
这是什么声音
Aah, what was that noise?
我不知道
I don't know.
什么情况
Give me a sit-rep.
好
Okay.
好 没有道理啊
Okay, this doesn't make any sense.
杀死她没有任何好处
There's no upside to killing her.
目前为止 他所做的一切都没有问题
He's made all the right moves, so far.
那么他到底在搞什么鬼
So what's the play?
他不能用白色货车来逃跑
He can't use the white van to get away...
Emily已经描述了它
Emily's description made sure of that.
Bishop 请回答
Bishop, report.
好吧 他不想冒险打电话
Okay, he doesn't want to risk calling.
但是他知道要是Emily没有尽快被发现
But he has to know if Emily isn't found ASAP,
【注：安珀警戒，美国在发生儿童绑架案时通过所有媒体向大众发布的警告】
他就会被安珀警戒全面通缉
he's looking at an AMBER Alert.
这样他就再也逃不了了
Then he'll never get away.
怎样才能找到她呢
So, how does she get found?
他在货车上喷了漆
He painted the van.
该死的
Damn it.
别走 别走 别走
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
你还好吗
You okay?
唔
Mm-hmm.
好的 你安全了
Okay, you're okay.
你安全了 我带你离开这好吗
You're okay. I'm gonna get you out of here, okay?
等下
Hang on.
爸爸
Dad. Oh.
妈妈
Mom.
真庆幸你没有事
I'm so glad you're all right.
我爱你
I love you.
我很担心你
I was so worried about you.
做得好
Nice work.
谢谢
Thanks. Yeah.
下次你再敢摘掉你的耳机
Next time you take your earwig out of your ear,
Bishop...
我就用订书机给你订上
I'm gonna use a staple gun.
好吧 呃 我担心
Yeah, uh, I was worried
如果Fornell夫妇发现了这个手机的话...
if the Fornells found out about the cell phone...
好的 好的 我明白
Yeah. Yeah, I know.
就像我刚说的...
Like I said...
做得好
Nice work.
谢谢
Thanks.
我还需要一个拥抱
I need another hug.
我真为你骄傲 亲爱的 我也是
I am so proud of you, baby. Oh, I am, too.
你没事吧 我还好 他没伤到我
- Are you really okay? - I'm fine. He didn't hurt me.
我只是担心你们这些人 你 你们都还好吧
I was just so worried about you guys-- are-are you okay?
是的 我们..还好
Oh, yeah, we're... Oh, oh, yeah.
真高兴我们又在一起了
We're just so happy that we're all together again.
你能平安归来
And we-we're just so glad that-that you're safe
我们都十分高兴
and you're back.
嗨 有什么发现吗
Hey, any word?
没有 在机场和火车站
Nothing. No sign at the airports
都没有发现他
or train station. McGee's
McGee正在和高速公路巡逻队沟通
talking to Highway Patrol, but I got a sinking feeling
但我有个不详的预感他应该是逃走了
he got away.
他逃不走的
Oh, he didn't get away.
毕竟我也是姓Fornell
My last name is Fornell, after all.
别动
Freeze.
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
不 你还是动的好
No. Move...
这样我就能开枪了
so I can shoot you.
我没有带手机
I'm not carrying a cell.
摩托车也不可能被追踪 你们怎么找到我的
This bike's untraceable. How'd you find me?
我们是没找到
We didn't.
我女儿找到的你
My daughter did.
跟她带警报器的开心猫手表
Say hello...
打个招呼吧
to her Happy Cat "Friend Alert" watch.
是内嵌蓝牙的
It's Bluetooth enabled.
只要方圆30尺内
It beeps any time a friend
有带同款手表的它就会自动响
wearing the same watch gets within 30 feet.
当然了 我不得不带上
Course, I had to boost the range on the second watch
另一只手表来追踪你
to track you, but...
这个小贱人
That little bitch.
嘴巴放干净点
Watch your mouth.
我不喜欢君子报仇十年不晚这类屁话
I'd hate to get suspended,
而且Gibbs探员也已经有了充足的证据
and Agent Gibbs already has enough paperwork.
我就不应该放她走
I should have never let her go.
抱歉 Gibbs
I'm sorry, Gibbs.
终于出气了
It's okay.
嗨
Hi.
早就说了他会走的
Eh, told you he'd run.
站住 站住
Hey! Hey, hey.
别走
Come on.
我们只是过来谢谢你的
We just came to say thank you.
你已经感谢过了
You already said thank you.
我们带了酒来
This time we brought liquor.
好吧 那我接受你们的谢意
Well, then, you're welcome.
还有...
And...
我们有个请求
And we have a request.
没完没了了
Oh, I can't wait.
你能不能不要别别扭扭了
Oh, will you stop with your whining?
我是说，你都是个成年人了
I mean, you're a grown man.
只 只是我们彼此都不能互相吸引而已 你在说什么
It-it's, it's unattractive. - What are you doing?
我们是来请他谅解的而你却刺激他
We're here to ask a favor and you're insulting the man.
自从我们到了这 他就像是丢了魂一样
He has been carrying on like he lost his dolly.
就没说过超过五个词的话
He hasn't said five words since he's got here.
噢...
Oh...
不管怎样
Anyway, we'll be out of your hair
我们一分钟内立马离开你的视线
in a minute.
只是...
It's just...
只是吧...
It's just that...
你也许已经注意到了
Well, uh, you've probably noticed that...
Tobias和我
Tobias and I--
已经得到教训了
clearly gluttons for punishment--
正在计划复婚
are trying to make a second go of things.
我们...
And, uh, we...
We, um...
我们...
We...
上帝保佑
Oh, for Pete's sake.
我们希望得到你的祝福
We want your blessing.
我的什么
My what?
你的祝福
Your blessing.
对Diane很重要
It's very important to Diane.
对我也很重要
And me.
我们需要你的祝福
That we have your blessing.
为什么
Why?
是因为...
Because it-it...
你哪来的那么多问题
What is with the 50 questions,do we have it or not?
==GA字幕组==
翻译:伯爵挠头写论文 小末要冻成蛇精了 小末末 飞行猪 菲力牛排和提拉米苏 秋水冬流
校对：流年想一觉不醒 Morning 蓉小张想泡温泉 K希望房东给点力
字幕特效/时间轴/压制：老东邪     军事顾问： Tom
飞行猪-Bishop是个萌妹子！
冰糖-又到了期末祈求学霸附体的时候T^T
小李-我是新人 望大家多多指教
小鹿-Fornell和Diane在一起了，Gibbs的春天在哪里？？？
伯爵- Fornell掉的头发都长在了……咳咳
流年-boss这集囧囧有神
蓉蓉-烦躁ing
佳晨-Diane的身材太好了
K-Tobias你怎么那么多话